To everyone at the Block Works Digital
Assets Summit, it's an honor to speak
with you about how the United States is
going to dominate crypto and the next
generation of financial technologies.
And it's not going to be easy, but we're
way ahead. Just two weeks ago, we hosted
the first ever White House digital asset
summit, bringing together many of the
world's top leaders in crypto for a
conversation led by our White House AI
and Cryptozar, David Sachs, who's a
fantastic and very brilliant guy. That
same week, I signed an order creating
the brand new strategic Bitcoin reserve
and the US digital asset stockpile,
which will allow the federal government
to maximize the value of its holdings
instead of foolishly selling them for a
fraction of their long-term value, which
is exactly what Biden did. He got a
fraction of their value. We're ending
the last administration's regulatory war
on crypto and Bitcoin. And that includes
stopping the lawless operation
chokepoint 2.0. Operation Chokepoint
went beyond regulation. And I mean far
beyond. It was a form of lawfare through
government weaponization. Frankly, it
was a disgrace. But as of January 20th,
2025, all of that is over. I've also
called on Congress to pass landmark
legislation creating simple common sense
rules for stable coins and market
structure. With the right legal
framework, institutions large and small
will be liberated to invest, innovate,
and take part in one of the most
exciting technological revolutions in
modern history. It's so big, it's I
think as big as you can get. Pioneers
like you will be able to improve our
banking and payment system and promote
greater privacy, safety, security, and
wealth for American consumers and
businesses alike. You will unleash an
explosion of economic growth. And with
the dollarbacked stable coins, you'll
help expand the dominance of the US
dollar and many, many years to come,
it'll be at the top. And that's where we
want to keep it. We only want to keep it
at the top always. I can already see
that the energy and passion of the
crypto community is the kind of spirit
that built our country. And it is
exciting to watch as you invent the
future of finance. And right here, it's
going to be right here in the USA, the
good old USA. Together, we will make
America the undisputed Bitcoin
superpower and the crypto capital of the
world. Thank you. Good luck. God bless
America.